Department of Physical Education and Athletics Records UA046
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Team files, 1874 -- 2011; 1970 -- 1990; UA046.001; 44.9 Linear Feet
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.145.00023 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.145.00024 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.145.00025 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.145.00026 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.145.00027 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.145.00028 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.145.00029 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.145.00030 (Box 145)
  - M Swim and Dive, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.145.00031 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.145.00032 (Box 145)
  - Men's Swim and Dive, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.145.00033 (Box 145)
  - M. Swimming, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.145.00034 (Box 145)
  - M. Swimming, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.001.145.00035 (Box 145)
  - Sailing, 2006 -- 2007; UA046.001.145.00036 (Box 145)
  - Sailing, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.145.00037 (Box 145)
  - Sailing, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.145.00038 (Box 145)
  - Sailing, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.146.00001 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.146.00002 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.146.00003 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.146.00004 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.146.00005 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.146.00006 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.146.00007 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.146.00008 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.146.00009 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.146.00010 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.146.00011 (Box 146)
  - Sailing, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.146.00012 (Box 146)
  - W. Basketball, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.146.00013 (Box 146)
  - W Basketball, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.146.00014 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.146.00015 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.146.00016 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.146.00017 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.146.00018 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.146.00019 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.146.00020 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.146.00021 (Box 146)
  - Women's Basketball, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.147.00001 (Box 147)
  - Women's Basketball, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.147.00002 (Box 147)
  - Women's Basketball, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.147.00003 (Box 147)
  - Women's Basketball, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.147.00004 (Box 147)
  - Women's Basketball, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.147.00005 (Box 147)
  - Women's Basketball, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.147.00006 (Box 147)
  - Women's Basketball, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.001.147.00007 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 2006; UA046.001.147.00008 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 2005; UA046.001.147.00009 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 2004; UA046.001.147.00010 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 2003; UA046.001.147.00011 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 2002; UA046.001.147.00012 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 2001; UA046.001.147.00013 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 2000; UA046.001.147.00014 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1999; UA046.001.147.00015 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1998; UA046.001.147.00016 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1997; UA046.001.147.00017 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1996; UA046.001.147.00018 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1995; UA046.001.147.00019 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1994; UA046.001.147.00020 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1993; UA046.001.147.00021 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1992; UA046.001.147.00022 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1991; UA046.001.147.00023 (Box 147)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1990; UA046.001.147.00024 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Team 1991 Memory Book, UA046.001.147.00025 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Team 1990 Memory Book, UA046.001.147.00026 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Team 1989 Memory Book, UA046.001.147.00027 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Team 1986 Memory Book, UA046.001.147.00028 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Team 1985 Memory Book, UA046.001.147.00029 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Team 1984 Memory Book, UA046.001.147.00030 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Team 1983 Memory Book, UA046.001.147.00031 (Box 147)
  - Note to Janet Silva from Bees Knees Club, 1984; UA046.001.147.00032 (Box 147)
  - Lacrosse Program, 2008; UA046.001.147.00033 (Box 147)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2006; UA046.001.147.00034 (Box 147)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2005; UA046.001.147.00035 (Box 147)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2004; UA046.001.147.00036 (Box 147)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2003; UA046.001.147.00037 (Box 147)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2002; UA046.001.147.00038 (Box 147)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2001; UA046.001.148.00001 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2000; UA046.001.148.00002 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1999; UA046.001.148.00003 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1998; UA046.001.148.00004 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse Scorebook, 1997; UA046.001.148.00005 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1997; UA046.001.148.00006 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse Scorebook, 1996; UA046.001.148.00007 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1996; UA046.001.148.00008 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse Scorebook, 1995; UA046.001.148.00009 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1995; UA046.001.148.00010 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse Scorebook, 1994; UA046.001.148.00011 (Box 148)
  - Lacrosse Rosters, 1994; UA046.001.148.00012 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1994; UA046.001.148.00013 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1993; UA046.001.148.00014 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1992; UA046.001.148.00015 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1991; UA046.001.148.00016 (Box 148)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1990; UA046.001.148.00017 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 2007; UA046.001.148.00018 (Box 148)
  - W Soccer, 2006; UA046.001.148.00019 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 2005; UA046.001.148.00020 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 2004; UA046.001.148.00021 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 2003; UA046.001.148.00022 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA046.001.148.00023 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 2001; UA046.001.148.00024 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 2000; UA046.001.148.00025 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1999; UA046.001.148.00026 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1998; UA046.001.148.00027 (Box 148)
  - Tufts Women's Soccer, 1998; UA046.001.148.00028 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1997; UA046.001.148.00029 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1996; UA046.001.148.00030 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1995; UA046.001.148.00031 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1994; UA046.001.148.00032 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer Scorebook, 1993; UA046.001.148.00033 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1993; UA046.001.148.00034 (Box 148)
  - Women's Soccer, 1992; UA046.001.148.00035 (Box 148)
  - W. Soccer, 1991; UA046.001.149.00001 (Box 149)
  - Women's Soccer, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.001.149.00002 (Box 149)
  - Women's Soccer, 1990; UA046.001.149.00003 (Box 149)
  - Women's Soccer, 1989; UA046.001.149.00004 (Box 149)
  - Women's Soccer Scorebook, 1984; UA046.001.149.00005 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 2006; UA046.001.149.00006 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 2005; UA046.001.149.00007 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 2004; UA046.001.149.00008 (Box 149)
  - Softball (folder 2 of 2), 2003; UA046.001.149.00009 (Box 149)
  - Softball (folder 1 of 2), 2003; UA046.001.149.00010 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 2002; UA046.001.149.00011 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 2001; UA046.001.149.00012 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 2000; UA046.001.149.00013 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1999; UA046.001.149.00014 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1998; UA046.001.149.00015 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1997; UA046.001.149.00016 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1996; UA046.001.149.00017 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1995; UA046.001.149.00018 (Box 149)
  - Tufts ECAC Champions 1995 Softball Sign, UA046.001.149.00019 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1994; UA046.001.149.00020 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1993; UA046.001.149.00021 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1992; UA046.001.149.00022 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1991; UA046.001.149.00023 (Box 149)
  - Softball, 1990; UA046.001.149.00024 (Box 149)
  - Tufts Swimming, 2009 -- 2010; UA046.001.149.00025 (Box 149)
  - Tufts Swimming, 2008 -- 2009; UA046.001.149.00026 (Box 149)
  - Tufts swimming, 2007 -- 2008; UA046.001.150.00001 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 2007 -- 2008; UA046.001.150.00002 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 2006 -- 2007; UA046.001.150.00003 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.150.00004 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.150.00005 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.150.00006 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.150.00007 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.150.00008 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.150.00009 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.150.00010 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.150.00011 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.150.00012 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.150.00013 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.150.00014 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.150.00015 (Box 150)
  - Tufts swimming, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.150.00016 (Box 150)
  - Women's swimming and diving, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.150.00017 (Box 150)
  - Women's swim and dive, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.151.00001 (Box 151)
  - Tufts swimming, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.151.00002 (Box 151)
  - Tufts swimming, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.151.00003 (Box 151)
  - Women's swim and dive, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.151.00004 (Box 151)
  - Tufts swimming, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.151.00005 (Box 151)
  - Women's swim and dive, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.151.00006 (Box 151)
  - Women's swim and dive, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.151.00007 (Box 151)
  - Tufts swimming, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.151.00008 (Box 151)
  - Tufts swimming, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.151.00009 (Box 151)
  - Women's swim and dive, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.151.00010 (Box 151)
  - Women's swim, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.151.00011 (Box 151)
  - Tufts swimming, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.151.00012 (Box 151)
  - Women's swimming, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.151.00013 (Box 151)
  - Women's s wim and dive 1993 New England Division III championship results, UA046.001.151.00014 (Box 151)
  - Women's swimming, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.151.00015 (Box 151)
  - Women's swimming, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.001.151.00016 (Box 151)
  - Meet results women's swim team, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.001.151.00017 (Box 151)
  - Typed meet results women's swim team, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.001.151.00018 (Box 151)
  - Typed meet results women's swim team, 1986 -- 1987; UA046.001.151.00019 (Box 151)
  - Typed meet results women's swim team, 1985 -- 1986; UA046.001.151.00020 (Box 151)
  - Typed meet results women's swim team, 1984 -- 1985; UA046.001.151.00021 (Box 151)
  - Typed results women's swim team, 1983 -- 1984; UA046.001.151.00022 (Box 151)
  - Meet results women's swim team, 1982 -- 1983; UA046.001.151.00023 (Box 151)
  - Women's tennis, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.151.00024 (Box 151)
  - Women's tennis, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.151.00025 (Box 151)
  - Women's tennis, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.151.00026 (Box 151)
  - Women's tennis, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.151.00027 (Box 151)
  - Women's Tennis, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.152.00001 (Box 152)
    Team Files
  - Women's Tennis, 2000; UA046.001.152.00002 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1999; UA046.001.152.00003 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1998; UA046.001.152.00004 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1997; UA046.001.152.00005 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1996; UA046.001.152.00006 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1995; UA046.001.152.00007 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1994; UA046.001.152.00008 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1993; UA046.001.152.00009 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1992; UA046.001.152.00010 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1991; UA046.001.152.00011 (Box 152)
  - Women's Tennis, 1990; UA046.001.152.00012 (Box 152)
  - Pre-Season FH, 1993; UA046.001.152.00013 (Box 152)
    Pre-season documents
  - Pre-Season Field Hockey, 1992; UA046.001.152.00014 (Box 152)
  - Pre-Season FH, 1991; UA046.001.152.00015 (Box 152)
  - Pre-Season FH, 1988; UA046.001.152.00016 (Box 152)
  - Pre-Season Hockey, 1986; UA046.001.152.00017 (Box 152)
  - FH, 2006; UA046.001.152.00018 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 2005; UA046.001.152.00019 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 2004; UA046.001.152.00020 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 2003; UA046.001.152.00021 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 2002; UA046.001.152.00022 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 2001; UA046.001.152.00023 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 2000; UA046.001.152.00024 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1999; UA046.001.152.00025 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1998; UA046.001.152.00026 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1997; UA046.001.152.00027 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1996; UA046.001.152.00028 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1995; UA046.001.152.00029 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1994; UA046.001.152.00030 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1993; UA046.001.152.00031 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1992; UA046.001.152.00032 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1991; UA046.001.152.00033 (Box 152)
  - Field Hockey, 1990; UA046.001.152.00034 (Box 152)
  - Women's T+F, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.152.00035 (Box 152)
  - Women's Indoor T+F, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.152.00036 (Box 152)
  - Women's Indoor, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.152.00037 (Box 152)
  - Women's indoor track and field, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.153.00001 (Box 153)
  - Women's track and field, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.153.00002 (Box 153)
  - Women's track and field, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.153.00003 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track and field, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.153.00004 (Box 153)
  - Women's track and field, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.153.00005 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.153.00006 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.153.00007 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.153.00008 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track and field, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.153.00009 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.153.00010 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track and field, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.153.00011 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.153.00012 (Box 153)
  - Women's indoor track and field, 1991; UA046.001.153.00013 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track, 2005; UA046.001.153.00014 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track and field, 2004; UA046.001.153.00015 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track and field, 2003; UA046.001.153.00016 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track and field, 2002; UA046.001.153.00017 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track and field, 2001; UA046.001.153.00018 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track and field, 2000; UA046.001.153.00019 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track, 1999; UA046.001.153.00020 (Box 153)
  - Women's track, 1998; UA046.001.153.00021 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track, 1997; UA046.001.153.00022 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track, 1996; UA046.001.153.00023 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track and field, 1995; UA046.001.153.00024 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track, 1994; UA046.001.153.00025 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track, 1993; UA046.001.153.00026 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track and field, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.153.00027 (Box 153)
  - Women and Men's track and field, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.001.153.00028 (Box 153)
  - Women's outdoor track, 1990; UA046.001.153.00029 (Box 153)
  - Volleyball, 2005; UA046.001.153.00030 (Box 153)
  - Volleyball, 2004; UA046.001.153.00031 (Box 153)
  - Volleyball, 2003; UA046.001.153.00032 (Box 153)
  - Volleyball, 2002; UA046.001.153.00033 (Box 153)
  - Volleyball, 2001; UA046.001.154.00001 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 2000; UA046.001.154.00002 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1999; UA046.001.154.00003 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1998; UA046.001.154.00004 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1997; UA046.001.154.00005 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1996; UA046.001.154.00006 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1995; UA046.001.154.00007 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1994; UA046.001.154.00008 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1993; UA046.001.154.00009 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1992; UA046.001.154.00010 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1991; UA046.001.154.00011 (Box 154)
  - Volleyball, 1990; UA046.001.154.00012 (Box 154)
  - Mens lacrosse publications, 2010 -- 2011; UA046.001.154.00013 (Box 154)
  - Mens lacrosse NCAA champ game, 2010; UA046.001.154.00014 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2006; UA046.001.154.00015 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2005; UA046.001.154.00016 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2004; UA046.001.154.00017 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2003; UA046.001.154.00018 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2002; UA046.001.154.00019 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2001; UA046.001.154.00020 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000; UA046.001.154.00021 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1999; UA046.001.154.00022 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1998; UA046.001.154.00023 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1997; UA046.001.154.00024 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1996; UA046.001.154.00025 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1995; UA046.001.154.00026 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1994; UA046.001.154.00027 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1993; UA046.001.154.00028 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1992; UA046.001.154.00029 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1991; UA046.001.154.00030 (Box 154)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1990; UA046.001.154.00031 (Box 154)
  - Hockey, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.155.00001 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.155.00002 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.155.00003 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.155.00004 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.155.00005 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.155.00006 (Box 155)
  - Hockey Team, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.155.00007 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.155.00008 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.155.00009 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.155.00010 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.155.00011 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.155.00012 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.155.00013 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.155.00014 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.155.00015 (Box 155)
  - Ice Hockey, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.155.00016 (Box 155)
  - Hockey, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.001.155.00017 (Box 155)
  - Baseball Scorebook, 2011; UA046.001.155.00018 (Box 155)
  - Baseball Scorebook, 1989; UA046.001.155.00019 (Box 155)
  - Baseball, 2006; UA046.001.155.00020 (Box 155)
  - Baseball, 2005; UA046.001.155.00021 (Box 155)
  - Baseball, 2004; UA046.001.155.00022 (Box 155)
  - Baseball, 2003; UA046.001.156.00001 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 2002; UA046.001.156.00002 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 2001; UA046.001.156.00003 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 2000; UA046.001.156.00004 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1999; UA046.001.156.00005 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1998; UA046.001.156.00006 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1997; UA046.001.156.00007 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1996; UA046.001.156.00008 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1995; UA046.001.156.00009 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1994; UA046.001.156.00010 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1993; UA046.001.156.00011 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1992; UA046.001.156.00012 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1991; UA046.001.156.00013 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1990; UA046.001.156.00014 (Box 156)
  - Baseball, 1985 -- 1986; UA046.001.156.00015 (Box 156)
    Schedule
  - Men's Hoops, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.156.00016 (Box 156)
  - M Basketball, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.156.00017 (Box 156)
  - Men's Basketball, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.001.157.00001 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.001.157.00002 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.001.157.00003 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.001.157.00004 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.001.157.00005 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.001.157.00006 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.001.157.00007 (Box 157)
  - Men's Hoops, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.001.157.00008 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.001.157.00009 (Box 157)
  - Men's Hoops, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.001.157.00010 (Box 157)
  - Men's Basketball, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.157.00011 (Box 157)
  - M. Basketball, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.157.00012 (Box 157)
  - Men's Hoops, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.001.157.00013 (Box 157)
  - M. Hoops, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.001.157.00014 (Box 157)
  - M. Basketball Team Stats, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.001.157.00015 (Box 157)
  - Football, 2002; UA046.001.157.00016 (Box 157)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.001.157.00017 (Box 157)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.001.158.00001 (Box 158)
  - Football, 1999; UA046.001.158.00002 (Box 158)
  - Football, 1998; UA046.001.158.00003 (Box 158)
  - Football, 1997; UA046.001.158.00004 (Box 158)
  - Football, 1996; UA046.001.158.00005 (Box 158)
  - Football Game Programs, 1995; UA046.001.158.00006 (Box 158)
  - Football, 1995; UA046.001.158.00007 (Box 158)
  - Football, 1994; UA046.001.158.00008 (Box 158)
    Team Files and Programs
  - Football, 1993; UA046.001.158.00009 (Box 158)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 2005; UA046.001.158.00010 (Box 158)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 2004; UA046.001.158.00011 (Box 158)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 2003; UA046.001.158.00012 (Box 158)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 2002; UA046.001.158.00013 (Box 158)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 2001; UA046.001.158.00014 (Box 158)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 2000; UA046.001.158.00015 (Box 158)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1999; UA046.001.159.00001 (Box 159)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1998; UA046.001.159.00002 (Box 159)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1997; UA046.001.159.00003 (Box 159)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1996; UA046.001.159.00004 (Box 159)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1995; UA046.001.159.00005 (Box 159)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1994; UA046.001.159.00006 (Box 159)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1993; UA046.001.159.00007 (Box 159)
  - Football Scoring Summaries, 1986; UA046.001.159.00008 (Box 159)
  - Football, 2007; UA046.001.159.00009 (Box 159)
  - Football, 2006; UA046.001.159.00010 (Box 159)
  - Football, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.159.00011 (Box 159)
  - Football, 2004; UA046.001.159.00012 (Box 159)
  - Football, 2003; UA046.001.159.00013 (Box 159)
  - M. Soccer, 2007; UA046.001.159.00014 (Box 159)
  - M. Soccer, 2006; UA046.001.159.00015 (Box 159)
  - M. Soccer, 2005; UA046.001.159.00016 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 2004; UA046.001.159.00017 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 2003; UA046.001.159.00018 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA046.001.159.00019 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 2001; UA046.001.159.00020 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 2000; UA046.001.159.00021 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1999; UA046.001.159.00022 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1998; UA046.001.159.00023 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1997; UA046.001.159.00024 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1996; UA046.001.159.00025 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1995; UA046.001.159.00026 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1994; UA046.001.159.00027 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.001.159.00028 (Box 159)
  - Men's Soccer, 1992; UA046.001.159.00029 (Box 159)
  - Men's soccer, 1991; UA046.001.160.00001 (Box 160)
  - Men's soccer, 1990; UA046.001.160.00002 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.001.160.00003 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.001.160.00004 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 2004; UA046.001.160.00005 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 2003; UA046.001.160.00006 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 2002; UA046.001.160.00007 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 2001; UA046.001.160.00008 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 2000; UA046.001.160.00009 (Box 160)
  - Men's Tennis, 1999; UA046.001.160.00010 (Box 160)